Hello everyone! Welcome to this video in which I'm trying on and styling four different dresses.
So this video is a collaboration with JJ's House. I was allowed to pick four dresses
and I felt like I'm in girly heaven because I don't own dresses that fluffy and huge and
And I barely knew what to pick and I'm super excited and curious how they'll look and how
they're going to fit with all the floof.
By the way, we're outdoor and filming in an industrial location today.
I hope you like it here.
Let's start with the green short one.
So it's a green dress for a change and not only black stuff today and I was allowed to
pick some accessories as well like this super awesome handbag and the jewelry and I combined
it with a metal delt I made myself and some latex leggings to make it a bit more me so
to say.
It's a bit itchy at the back where the sequins scrub at my skin on the edge but otherwise
it fits really good and there's a lot of volume going on.
And the shoes are from JJ's house as well.
Since they're black I'll use them for the other dresses as well.
up is this two-piece set consisting of a top and a really long skirt and I combined it with a hat
also from JJ's house and a clutch. I think it's a super cool combination also with the two pieces.
I can use the skirt for other outfits like combining it with a corset or just using the
top for a leggings outfit or another skirt. So this is really handy to do multiple stylings with.
This is the ball gown I ordered because I tried to cover as many dress types as possible.
And I combined it with this headpiece which I bought last year at the Amphi festival.
and I've been dying to find another occasion to wear it so I think it looks
perfect together with this dress. All of these dresses have built-in bras so you
don't need to wear bra underneath which is pretty essential for this dress for
example because a back cleavage or whatever you may call it is really deep
so there's no interrupting bra action. So I think this was the most expensive
dress of all four but it's also the widest one so to say with five layers of
fabric and this cool detail belt here. And one final look with a red dress
because I wanted to have another bold color in the selection and I combined it
with latex gloves to give it a bit more edge and character and this one is a
rather tight gown this time. The back looks really interesting with all the
straps and I combined the dress with another pair of shoes. This time they're
black and red ones so they'll fit great together.
Okay, so that was it. I had a lot of fun styling these dresses. I'm really happy that they all fit and that they look good. I think my favorite one was the poofy ball gown with the headpiece because I really like the gothic look.
But I love the other ones as well, especially with all the accessories.
When you order there, it's going to take a while until the items arrive,
because you can choose the color and then they're going to
sew the dresses right away for you.
I'm really glad that they all fit really good.
I didn't expect that to be honest,
because I have no experience with buying dresses.
But everything turned out really good.
If you're looking for some affordable dresses and everything you need to style them, like shoes,
bags, jewelry and stuff like that, go check out JJ's house. I can really recommend them.
Have a good day, see ya, bye!